What if your entire video workflow, from fetching raw footage to posting branded shorts on every social platform, ran completely on autopilot?
Every day, content creators and agencies waste hours downloading videos, editing them into shorts, adding captions, writing taglines, and manually posting to YouTube, TikTok, Instagram, and Facebook.
It's repetitive, exhausting, and it doesn't scale.
Introducing Video Workflow Manager.
A powerful automation engine that fetches your videos, converts them into branded shorts with AI captions and taglines, and posts them everywhere, automatically.
Connect any video source.
Bunny CDN, FTP servers, or any cloud storage.
The system fetches your videos automatically with smart date filtering and rotation to ensure every video gets processed.
FFmpeg powers the video engine.
Convert any video into six different aspect ratios: vertical for Shorts and Reels, square for feeds, or widescreen.
Choose crop or fit mode.
Set custom durations and let the smart segment selector find the best starting point.
Auto-generate captions in over twenty languages with OpenAI Whisper.
Word-level timestamps ensure perfectly synced subtitles that are burned directly into your videos for maximum engagement.
Never run out of creative taglines.
The AI engine uses Google Gemini or OpenAI to generate unique, engaging text for every single video.
Plus, a built-in library of over five thousand viral taglines with emojis as an instant fallback.
Post to nine platforms simultaneously.
YouTube Shorts, TikTok, Instagram Reels, Facebook, Threads, X, LinkedIn, Pinterest, and Bluesky.
Schedule posts with custom timing, stagger them for maximum reach, or publish immediately.
Set it and forget it.
Schedule automations to run every few minutes, hourly, daily, or weekly.
The built-in cron system handles everything with live progress tracking, detailed logs, and automatic error recovery.
Built with battle-tested technology.
PHP backend running on XAMPP, MySQL database with auto-migration, FFmpeg for video processing, and a modern dark-themed dashboard powered by Tailwind CSS.
Everything self-hosted, fully under your control.
The numbers speak for themselves.
Nineteen thousand lines of production code, two hundred forty three functions, twenty three API endpoints, nine social platforms, six aspect ratios, and five thousand plus taglines ready to go.
Here's the complete workflow in action.
Configure once: set your video source, choose your style, enable AI features, select platforms.
Then hit start.
The engine fetches, processes, brands, captions, and posts, all automatically, every single time.
Ready to automate your entire video pipeline?
Video Workflow Manager is your all-in-one solution for content automation at scale.
Self-hosted, fully customizable, and built to save you hours every single day.
Let's get started.