What if your entire video workflow ran completely on autopilot?
No more manual editing.
No more repetitive posting.
Just pure automation.
Every day, content creators waste hours downloading videos, editing them into shorts, writing captions, and manually posting to every platform.
It's exhausting and it doesn't scale.
Introducing Video Workflow Manager.
The all-in-one automation engine that handles everything for you.
Step one: Connect your video source.
Bunny CDN, FTP servers, or any cloud storage.
The system fetches videos automatically with smart filtering and rotation.
Step two: FFmpeg converts every video into six aspect ratios.
Vertical for shorts, square for feeds, widescreen for YouTube.
Crop or fit mode, custom durations, high quality encoding.
Step three: AI-powered captions.
OpenAI Whisper transcribes in over twenty languages with word-level timestamps.
Subtitles are burned directly into your videos.
Step four: Never run out of taglines.
Google Gemini or OpenAI generates unique text for every video.
Plus five thousand built-in viral taglines with emoji overlays.
Step five: Post to nine platforms simultaneously.
YouTube Shorts, TikTok, Instagram Reels, Facebook, Threads, X, LinkedIn, Pinterest, and Bluesky.
Scheduled or immediate.
Step six: Set it and forget it.
Automations run every few minutes, hourly, daily, or weekly.
Live progress tracking, detailed logs, and automatic error recovery.
The numbers speak for themselves.
Nineteen thousand lines of code, two hundred forty three functions, twenty three API endpoints, nine social platforms, and five thousand plus taglines.
Here's the magic.
Configure once, set your video source, choose your style, enable AI features, select platforms, hit start.
The engine runs automatically, every single time.
Ready to automate your entire video pipeline?
Video Workflow Manager.
Self-hosted, fully customizable, built to save you hours every single day.
Let's get started.